The stock market is buzzing with news of
several companies making headlines.
Here are some of the top stocks in news
as of January 10th 2026.
Gujarat Kidney and Super Specialtity
after raising Rs 250.80
cr via IPO. The company is making its
stock market debut.
Barat Electronics, the state-run defense
major, has received additional orders
worth Rs 569 cr since December 12th.
Grazim Industries, the company board has
approved a composite scheme of
arrangement among several entities.
Lupin the pharma major has entered into
an exclusive license, supply and
distribution agreement with GAN and Lee
Pharmaceuticals.
Wari Energies Amit Pancar has resigned
from the position of wholetime director
and chief executive officer. These
stocks are expected to remain under
spotlight as they continue to attract
attention due to their recent
developments and market performance.
Quarterly business updates.
Signature global Q3. Yo Y pre-sales down
27% to Rs 2020 cr. VSRs 2770
cr. Area sold falls 42% to 1.44 million
SQT. VS2.49
million SQT. Collections grow 14% to Rs
1,230
cr. VSRs 1,080 cr.
Phoenix Mills Q3 yo y retail portfolio
consumption rises 20% to ours 4,787
cr. Q3 reflected a period of strong
operational execution.
Retail consumption delivers doubledigit
growth during festive period. St. Regis
Mumbai delivers refp growth of 10%.
Gross residential sales surged to Rs 140
crore. VSRs 58 crore. Ashana housing Q3
YO area booked falls 17.9%
to 5.56 cr. Lock sq foot vs 6.77 lock
sqt value of area sold drops 11.7% to
ours 41.07
cr. VSRs 454.16
cr embassy development Q3 Qoq
pre-sales zooms to Rs 1,392
cr VSRs 49 cr collections grow 15.6% 6%
to Rs 4515 cr VSRs 359 crerly
earnings
Avenue supermart Q3 consolidated YOI
profit jumps 18.3% to Rs 855.9
cr VSRs 723.7
cr revenue grows 13.3% to Rs 18,100.88
88 crore. VSRs 15,972.6
cr board appoints on scholasawa
presently the CEO designate as chief
executive officer and key managerial
personnel of the company. Indian
renewable energy development agency
hired a Q3 yo profit spikes 37.6%
to Rs 585.2
cr VSRs 425.4
4 cr. Net interest income jumps 34.7%
to Rs 897.2
cr. VSRs 666.3
cr. monthly business update
Mahindra and Mahindra December. YoY
sales volume sinks 27.1%
to 85,51
units vs 67,252
units.
Exports fall 9.3% to 2,849
units. VS3,142
units.
Production source 25.4%
to 68,992
units. VS55,015
units.
Disclaimer. This article provides stock
market news forformational purposes only
and should not be construed as
investment advice. Readers are
encouraged to consult with a qualified
financial adviser before making any
investment decisions.